Hope.
霍普
Look at me.
看着我
I'm expendable.
他可以牺牲我
That's why I'm here.
这就是我在这儿的原因
You must've realized that by now.
你现在一定明白了吧
I mean, that's why I'm in the suit and you're not.
这就是为什么是我来穿战衣而不是你
He'd rather lose this fight than lose you.
他宁愿输掉这一战也不愿失去你
anyway.
算了吧
You know, I didn't know you had a daughter,
当时我报警的时候
when I called the cops on you.
我并不知道你有个女儿
What's her name?
她叫什么
Cassie.
凯茜
It's a pretty name.
好名字
You have to clear your mind, Scott.
你必须清除杂念 斯科特
You have to make your thoughts precise,
你脑海里的思路必须精准
that's how it works.
那样才行
Think about Cassie,
想想凯茜
about how badly you want to see her,
想想你多么想见她
and use that to focus.
用这样来集中精神
Open your eyes,
睁开眼睛
and just think about what you want the ants to do.
专心去想你要让蚂蚁做什么
That's good.
很好